Hi, I'm James from Reptile Rescue Service in Salt Lake City, Utah.
If your turtle won't eat, that's the topic of this one, this discussion here.
There could be a couple of variances of this one.
Could be, if it's a wild caught turtle, land turtle or tortoise, a lot of time they sense in they sense in the wintertime, it's time to hibernate.
At this time they'll quit eating, because if they have food in their belly when they go into hibernation, it can be fatal.
It'll actually ferment or rot, and can cause fatality to the turtle or tortoise.
Another sign of this could be if they have an upper respiratory infection, which is like a form of pneumonia to us humans.
It makes them weak and sick.
If it's a Russian tortoise, a lot of these carry herpes disease.
This is not contagious to humans, but it is to other tortoises.
So if you have one that has this disease, you need to keep 'em separate.
This will affect 'em on eating, and also they will be lazy and want to sleep a lot.